[
    {
        "question": "The biggest and most famous monument in Paris is...",
        "choices": [
            "Stonehenge",
            "Colosseum",
            "Eiffel Tower",
            "Statue of Liberty"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which monument was the gift of the French Government to the US?",
        "choices": [
            "Statue of Liberty",
            "Eiffel Tower",
            "The Vatican",
            "Great Sphinx"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "A massive monument on the Salisbury Plain in southern England is...",
        "choices": [
            "The Vatican",
            "Stonehenge",
            "Colosseum",
            "Great Sphinx"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "One of the amazing wonders of ancient Egyptian architecture adjoining the Pyramids of Giza is...",
        "choices": [
            "Colosseum",
            "Eiffel Tower",
            "Great Sphinx",
            "Stonehenge"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The largest and the most famous of the Roman amphitheaters is...",
        "choices": [
            "Stonehenge",
            "Colosseum",
            "Eiffel Tower",
            "Statue of Liberty"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is a group of buildings in Rome comprising the official residence of the Pope?",
        "choices": [
            "Stonehenge",
            "The Vatican",
            "Eiffel Tower",
            "Statue of Liberty"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Stonehenge is thought to have been constructed from...",
        "choices": [
            "3000 BCE to 2000 BCE",
            "2000 BCE to 1000 BCE",
            "1000 BCE to 100 BCE",
            "100 BCE to 100 CE"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Stonehenge may have been used as an...",
        "choices": [
            "Astronomical observatory",
            "Royal Palace",
            "Military fortress",
            "Grain storage"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Stonehenge measures...",
        "choices": [
            "Solar movements only",
            "Lunar movements only",
            "Solar and lunar movements",
            "Water movements"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is Colosseum?",
        "choices": [
            "Paris",
            "Rome",
            "England",
            "Egypt"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    }
]